<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Busfahrer</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="placeholder_ipsum">The bus driver game is a card game that is played with 52 cards. You can play it alone or with multiple players. Of course it is more fun with friends than alone. The game starts with four guessing rounds. In the first round, the player has to guess whether the symbol on the card is red or black. In the second round whether the rank of the card is higher or lower than the first card. In the third round whether the card is inside the outside of the first two cards. In the last round, the player has to guess the symbol of the card. The next game round is the pyramid round. Here the player has to compare his cards from the guessing rounds with the cards from the pyramid round and find a matching card. The last game round is the bus driver round. The player with the most points must correctly guess 4 cards to win. However, if he hits a face card, the round starts again. The special thing about the game is that there are cheat functions in every round. Other players can catch the player cheating and reveal them. In the bus driver circuit, for example, the cheat button shows all cards for a certain time.
    </string>
    <!-- Spieleranzahl StartServer -->
    <string-array name="spieleranzahl">
        <item>2</item>
        <item>3</item>
        <item>4</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="title_activity_wait">waitActivity</string>
    <string name="dummy_button">Dummy Button</string>
    <string name="dummy_content">DUMMY\nCONTENT</string>
    <string name="plab_header">Pyramiden Lab</string>
    <string name="card_backcover">🂠</string>
    <string name="plab_nextButton">Next Lap</string>
    <string name="plab_selectButton">Deal Points</string>
    <string name="deal_button_text">Deal Points</string>
    <string name="host_input_label">Enter Server IP Address</string>
    <string name="button_erwischt">Erwischt!</string>
</resources>
